guifx.com 2008-12-24

# Guifx:

Toll Free Support: 1 (888) 33-GUIFX

**Privacy Policy**

**Guifx** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

**IP Addresses and Cookies**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address and cookie file is used to help identify you and your personal profile, track shopping cart items, and track your access via .htaccess requests, where applicable. 

**Personal Information**  
Our site uses a variety of feedback and/or registration forms, order forms, online survey forms, and submission forms which require users to give us contact information (like name and email address). The user's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Contact information from these forms may also be used to send information about our company and scheduled events, merchandise specials, contests, or other information relating to **Guifx** and its strategic partners. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

**Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. **Guifx** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**  
This site employs security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Subscription Mailing List**  
If you have subscribed to our mailing list and now wish to remove yourself from it, you may do so via the included unsubscribe link located inside all of our sent email correspondence. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service and cancel their subscriptions. 

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us.
